Come on, Shi Ho Ho, let's sing it together
Sadness melts in my mouth and I'm waiting for the time to sprout
I don't think I'm fresh enough and I don't think I can sing well enough.
I don't think Terap is very good at singing.
I think we need a girl who can raise the foundation of her singing.
I think we need more variety in the group.
I would like to have a girl who can make Pillarpaw more interesting and exciting.
I hope that a new wind will blow in PillarPaw
I hope that a new wind will blow in PillarPaw and we will be able to show a different PillarPaw.
I want to shine in the center
It was the first dream that I wanted to be the only one.
It was the first dream that I wanted to be the best and the only one that I wanted to be.
I'm confident that I've practiced the hardest among all of them.
I'm getting closer to what I wanted to do, step by step.
I took this as my last chance.
I really felt like this is where my life was going to end.
We were all unhappy as it was.
I'm sorry, but what do you think I'm going to do?
Go!
The audition camp for new members was held in April at Lake Yamanaka in Yamanashi Prefecture. It had been about a month since I had met the finalists since their unveiling on March 6.
Aren't you two a little fast in your turnaround?
No, I'm just a little fired up. Good morning. No, no ... Good morning, everyone. Good morning. We are finally going to decide on a new member for the April 19 show at the Quattro.
Yes, the purpose of this camp is the subjects of the assigned songs to be performed at the new member presentation on April 19.
It will be the first time for me to see the finalists sing and dance, and I am looking forward to seeing how they will perform! The song for the new member audition
The song is a baton peel written for the new member audition, and it is a song with the meaning of passing the baton from Japple to the new members.
This time, we will be divided into two teams, A and B, to perform the song.
The song will be performed by two teams, A and B. The members of the A team are from Shizuoka Prefecture, and the members of the B team are from Japan.
The A team member is Rena Sakurai, a second-year high school student from Shizuoka Prefecture.
My strength is my competitive spirit,
I want to shine at the center. Saki Hasegawa used to be an idol until two years ago.
Saki Hasegawa, who had been active as an idol until two years ago, learned that there was an audition for Fill-a-Porter, which she had been longing for, and decided to become an idol again.
She decided to become an idol again.
She was unable to attend a live concert during the summer stoppage live show.
Instead, she was helping the idols with shaved ice.
While making shaved ice, I thought it was wonderful and wanted to be a part of it.
So it was like you were passing the baton to me?
Yeah.
Yeah. That's how I felt.
Ms. Yuuga Ayamori is a current music student.
She's always had a passion for music.
Three years ago, she learned of the existence of Piluppo, and began to yearn for it.
It was the first time she got to know Pilapo.
She was very excited to take the class.
She was not able to find one that she wanted to be a part of,
When I saw Pilapo's audition for the first time, I knew I had to do it,
I thought, "I have no choice but to do this," and I immediately applied.
Shiori Ichihara, 21, has auditioned for many idols.
I took this one because I thought it was my last chance. Shiori Ichihara, 21 years old, has been undergoing idol auditions.
I thought it was my last chance, so I took a chance on this one.
At the end of Team A, she seemed to be behind in both dance and singing. Ms. Aokawa wanted to do it herself, which was lower than the other kids in practical skills.
Mr. Aokawa, by actually dancing,
She learned the feeling of dancing.
Ms. Aokawa learned the feeling of dancing.
Because I am aokara,
I live by momentum, so I guess I try my best with momentum and learn the choreography.
One, two, three, four, rock, paper, scissors.
This is Ohsato-san's, Shiori-chan is in the center, 1, 2, 3, 4, cha, cha.
This is Ohsato-san's, with Shiori-chan in the center and Aki-chan in the first row, number 3,
Yes, yes, yes!
Here it is, 1.5.
Cha, cha, ta, da, ta,
Ta, ta, ta, ta, ta, ta, ta,
Cha, cha, cha, ta, ta, ta, ta, ta,
One, two, three, four, cha-chang-oh-oh-oh.
Ooh-ooh-ooh.
There it is.
LOL!
Mr. Aokawa still has a lot of issues to work on.
But his passion for the tiruapodition
is very serious about it.
I used to like Lynn Asamura.
There was an audition for TikTok's Til-A audition that I was betting on, but I failed after 3 days.
But I still wanted to be an idol for a long time, so I will always be an idol.
I thought that Yuki-chan was not good at dancing, so it would be great if I could see how she could digest the stop motion into her performance.
It was impressive to see Aokawa-san practicing without any hesitation. I was impressed by the way Aokawa-san kept practicing. I want him to stop at a cute line rather than going overboard,
Don, don, jan, jan, don, don, jan, jan, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Big time, big time, and then we all kind of hold hands in a line.
Yes, yes, yes... The oldest member is 21-year-old Risa Yamanaka, who specializes in karate. She is 21 years old and thought it would be her last time to be an idol, so she applied for the position.
Ms. Suzu Yamazaki has been performing since she was a child. Thanks for your hard work. When I was in my first year of high school.
I had a contract that
I let it expire.
My friend liked Ms. Piruapo.
As I got to know Mr. Pilupo
I thought, "I want to be like this once more.
I wanted to be like this once again.
When I saw Mr. Pilupo
I was able to reaffirm it,
I was able to reaffirm it.
In Team B, there were three members who had no experience in either dancing or singing.
The youngest was Runa Minami, a second-year high school student.
Madoka Flamegami, 19, is from Yamagata Prefecture and usually attends her university's hogaku club.
Sena Hiroshima, who just entered college this spring.
At first I kind of admired her, because I like singing and dancing too,
I thought, "I want to be an idol.
When I think about the formations and so on.
It's different from what I remembered.
I think it is very difficult.
I have no experience, so I have to catch up,
I have no choice but to practice hard.
You have to start from here,
Feet?Feet?
Feet.
Which way are you going?
Left.
Left, when you do boom,
Boom, boom, boom, boom. Once you do boom, boom, boom, choo-choo, choo-choo.
Once you do "boom", this leg goes flying, too. With a pop.
Yes, yes, boom, clang, clang. That's right.
Miminami asked the teacher immediately when she didn't understand something, and actively worked on it.
She was actively working on it.
Ms. Onoue said, "I have had many lessons in the past, but I have never been able to finish them,
I want to do my best in what I love and not let myself be defeated. Have you ever done it while dancing? While going down? Oh, I'll be dancing.
It's kind of hard.
Wow.
Yes, it is.
I'll explain Soo-chan's moves to you.
In the meantime, the four of you
a little bit
Dancing, dancing, dancing, dancing...
Dancing, dancing, dancing, dancing... Oh, that? Wait, wait. That's right.
I'll explain Soo-chan's moves, and in the meantime, I'd like the four of you to practice on your own.
Okay.
Chi-chan is beautiful, isn't she?
Where shall we start?
From the very beginning, from the very beginning, you're making mistakes, so there's mud all over the place.
It's so bad!
It smells good.
It's okay. It's okay.
Just take your time.
You want to start from the beginning?
Yeah, let's start from the beginning.
I've always loved idols.
I'm slower than everyone else.
But I can't do it.
But I'm confident that I've practiced the most.
I'm confident that I've practiced the most.
But it's not so easy to learn...
Are you okay?
You're so cute.
I have a flat tire.
I don't know what to do.
Don't worry about it.
I'll be fine.
I'll do my best, I'll do my best, I'll do my best!
The person who comforted Ms. Hondaibe closest to her was Sena Hiroshima
I've always wanted to be an idol.
I had always wanted to be an idol, but even if I made it to the final round, I sometimes failed.
To be honest, I thought it was too much. I had always wanted to be an idol, but even if I made it to the final round, I sometimes failed,
I had already given up on the idea of becoming an idol, but when I saw this audition, I was a little concerned,
But when I saw this audition, I was a little bit interested in the group,
I was really attracted by the group's performance and the members who danced with all their might at every performance,
I was attracted by the group's live performances and the members who danced their hearts out in every scene, and I applied for the group on a hunch that I wanted to join.
I have not had a dream since I was a child,
Idol was the only dream I wanted to have. It was my first dream, so I want to make it come true.
I want it to come true.
I think Senna is amazing,
She is very fast at dancing,
Recently, we have been practicing dancing together,
We also practice singing karaoke together.
Onoue and Hiroshima are beginners who have been practicing together for the camp.
Three of the five members of the B team had never danced before,
I saw Ms. Yamanaka, who has dance experience, taking the lead in teaching them many times.
When you go to zero, three centimeters in front of the zero, you do it facing the other way.
You have to do it facing the other way, tan-tan-tan,
When Chuchu-chan goes to 0, how about to 0?
Tintin-tintin.
Of course, each individual has to work hard,
But we have a goal to make something good as a group,
I think that we are able to improve each other. The only thing that overflowed was that one word.
It will continue after this.
All the way.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you very much.
It was a great teamwork between everyone.
I know you've been watching each and every one of our dancers.
I want you to have confidence in that.
Don't worry about what you can't do during the lesson.
You don't have to worry too much about what you can't do during the lesson.
On the other hand, Mr. Aokawa of A team struggled with inexperienced dancers.
Ms. Nishiwaki, who also has dance experience, is teaching Ms. Aokawa.
Ms. Nishiwaki, who also has dance experience, is teaching Ms. Aokawa. I'm really thinking about it. I'll ask him to teach me. I made a promise.
I've been doing it for 8 years.
What kind of dance?
I've been doing mostly jazz, hip-hop, and rock,
I have to do rock and roll.
I also did a little ballet and physical manipulation.
I'm doing a full combo.
Today's official practice menu is all done.
It's time for the long awaited dinner.
I'm going to have it.
Not a single person is left-handed.
I am left-handed, but only chopsticks are right.
Oh, I see.
You seem to have a good brain. Your brain looks good.
Your brain looks good.
Among the smiling finalists who successfully completed the first day of the competition
One of them had a buoyant expression on his face.
Hmmm, this is the part I remember.
Huh?
My shrimp.
I'll take it.I'll take it.
They're my prawns, and you said I was the weakest.
I'm not weak.
They're tender.
Delicious.
BGM
BGM BGM
BGMBGM BGMBGM BGMBGM BGMBGM BGMBGM
Excuse me, sir.
You cold?
It's cold.
The finalists gathered voluntarily in the gymnasium after entering the office and started practicing.
The finalists started practicing.
Before we knew it, all 10 of us had gathered.
♪ Music
I was right in the back and just when I was here
It was like all of a sudden it was going to pass.
I'll put it along here.
♪ Music
Which is where we're going from, because we're only moving 5.
I'm not used to that place like that.
It's just that everyone's been leaning this way too much.
Actually, it's three, one, two, zero.
Three Viper Keys, so...
Okay. Okay.
I'll take Viper Key's three.
At this point, I'm rooting for you.
I'm rooting for you, I'm rooting for you, and lastly, are you standing up for the guy who's standing up for you?
I'm standing up.
Oh, but left, when I head left.
I'm going left, and you're going right when I change.
Oh, I see.
I'm going left.
I was also impressed by the way they crossed team boundaries and exchanged opinions with each other.
Those who came to the venue were,
They are so close to each other that it's hard to believe that they are rivals.
I think the A team has a lot of individuality. The way they dance, the way they make art, everything.
They are like idols. They're so cute.
They're like the Hoop Ridge team. Yes, they are.
The 10 finalists, this one is the crew, and the one in front of them is Elle, what's her name?
What's that? Center, center, center.
You talk a lot.
That's you, right? We're going to be a force to be reckoned with.
I'm supported by so many people.
Even their kindness
Sometimes we forget
Or they put it away.
Here is something warm and fuzzy
You can't do anything about it
Just thinking about it without being able to do anything about it
Anyone can do that
I'm sure that when I was about to fall
From the day you reached out to me
I've been on a journey to find what I want to do for you
me
me me me me me me me me me me me me me me me me me me me me me me me me
This puzzle will continue
forever
The trials are over.
I did my best
Yay!
I did my best tomorrow, too. Yay! I'll do my best again tomorrow!
It was fun. I'll do my best tomorrow too.
I was doing Luna's palate.
What?
Left, right, left, right.
Left, right, left, right! Left, right, left, right.
Yes!
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
A-ha-ha-ha!
Cut, cut, cut.
Ha-ha-ha-ha
Next time, the second half of the camp ... Okkun, good luck, good luck to us, good luck to us, good luck to us